(DRIVER WHIMPERING)
Oh!
Oh, no!
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: Oh.
(WIND HOWLING)
(TEETH CHATTERING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Phew!
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LAUGHTER)
(EXCLAIMING GLEEFULLY)
Hyah, hyah! Whoo!
Okay, everybody,
time to start.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(ALL GIGGLING)
Come a little closer.
(LAUGHING)
Wow.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Who's ready for Elf training?
Me!
Me, me!
Hit it, boys!
(ALL WHOOPING)
(SINGING) So, stomp your
feet and give a twerk
When the music plays
we get to work
We work all night
we work all day
We put the toys
in Santa's sleigh
(LAUGHING)
(TRAIN WHISTLE TOOTING)
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
(GASPS AND GRUNTS)
(CACKLING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(STRAINING)
(YELLS)
That's not...
(GROANING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
All right, let's train you
for something else.
Huh?
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
(YELLING)
(GASPING)
(ELVES GASPING)
(SPITS)
I know the perfect job
for you guys.
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(SIGHS)
Oh! Aw...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(WHIMPERING)
Oh.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS MENACINGLY)
(WHISTLES)
(REINDEER GRUNTING)
No, no, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
Huh? (LAUGHS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL YELLING)
(LAUGHING)
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
(YELLING)
You've ruined everything!
You'll never be elves!
(GASPS)
Huh?
Ow!
(MINION GROANS)
SANTA: Ho-ho-ho!
(GASPS) Santa's coming!
(MINIONS YELLING)
(ALL GIBBERING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(MINIONS SCREAMING)
Huh.
(MINIONS GROANING)
(GIGGLING)
SANTA: Ho-ho-ho!
(CHUCKLES)
Ahem, your sleigh is
all ready, Santa!
(ALL CHEERING)
(CRASHING)
(ALL NEIGHING)
Wait! (GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
Trainees! Am I right?
(GROANS)
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
(REINS WHIPPING)
(ALL WHOOPING)
(MINIONS SINGING IN MINIONESE)